(Sheldon:)You'll hear a slight click.
(Penny:)Hang on. Sheldon, do you have
any emotional attachment to this box?
(Sheldon:)No. It's a novelty I ordered off the Internet.
Did you hear the click?
(Penny:)Not yet.
(Penny:)There it is.
(Howard:)Okay, here's another one.
(Howard:)If you married the famous rock guitarist
Johnny Winter...
(Howard:)...you'd be Summer Winter.
- Uh-huh.
- Yep.
Okay, I'm gonna just go for broke here
and say I like you.
(Summer:)Yeah?
So here's my question:
Do you see any conversational path that
would take us from where we are now...
(Howard:)...to a place where I could ask you out
and you'd say yes?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Howard:)Fair enough. I'll leave you in peace.
(Leonard:)Thank you.